{
  "aow.trivia": [
    {
      "question": "What is the correct pronunciation of Sakura Blade?",
      "type": "multiple",
      "choices": ["Gen-i-chi-ro", "Ge-ni-chi-ro", "Gen-ni-chi-ro"],
      "correct-answer": 0,
      "order": "random"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the symbol on Ivan’s cape?",
      "type": "multiple",
      "choices": ["Crown", "Sword", "Shield", "No symbol"],
      "correct-answer": 0,
      "order": "random"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the symbol on Arthur’s cape?",
      "type": "multiple",
      "choices": ["Crown", "Sword", "Lightening", "No symbol"],
      "correct-answer": 3,
      "order": "random"
    },
    {
      "question": "What weapon do brawlers weld? ",
      "type": "multiple",
      "choices": ["Axe", "Sword", "Spear", "Harpoon"],
      "correct-answer": 0,
      "order": "random"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following troops does not have horns?",
      "type": "multiple",
      "choices": ["Taurus Witcher", "Yasha", "Demon", "They all have horns"],
      "correct-answer": 3,
      "order": "fixed"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following colors best describes the attire of enemy __Undead Warrior__?",
      "type": "multiple",
      "choices": ["Dark purple", "Dark red", "Dark green", "Camouflage"],
      "correct-answer": 0,
      "order": "random"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following colors best describes the attire of enemy __Shadow Ninja__?",
      "type": "multiple",
      "choices": ["Bright red", "Dark red", "Dark green", "Dark blue"],
      "correct-answer": 0,
      "order": "random"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which troops does not have wings?",
      "type": "multiple",
      "choices": ["Ghost Assassins", "Hell Jailers", "Undead Soldier", "Demon"],
      "correct-answer": 0,
      "order": "random"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following troops does not carry a shield?",
      "type": "multiple",
      "choices": ["Pilgrims", "Brawlers", "Skeletons", "Paladin", "They all carry shields"],
      "correct-answer": 4,
      "order": "fixed"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many tentacles does Kraken have",
      "type": "multiple",
      "choices": ["6", "7", "8", "10"],
      "correct-answer": 2,
      "order": "fixed"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which hero is not of Marksman profession?",
      "type": "multiple",
      "choices": ["Athena", "Robin Hood", "Apollo", "Freyja"],
      "correct-answer": 0,
      "order": "random"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which hero is not of Support Profession?",
      "type": "multiple",
      "choices": ["Jinn", "Selene", "Hoheheim", "Edward", "They are all Support heroes"],
      "correct-answer": 4,
      "order": "fixed"
    }
  ]
}